xtremepapers.com 2012-12-31

# Privacy Statement - XtremePapers | Advancing knowledge is in our DNA

## Privacy Statement

If you are affiliated with any government, police, anti-piracy group or other related group or working for Adidas, Manobo Blahnik, Converse, Louis Vuitton, Chanel, Burberry, Hermes, Prada, Air Jordan, Nike, Timberland, Gucci, Cartier, Oakley, CIE, British council, TCS either directly or indirectly, or any other related group, or were formally a worker, you CANNOT enter these webpages, links, nor access any of its files and you cannot view any of the HTML files. If in fact you are affiliated or were affiliated with the above said companies, by entering this site you are not agreeing to these terms and you are violating code 431.322.12 of the Internet Privacy Act signed by Bill Clinton in 1995 and that means that you CANNOT threaten our ISP(s) or any person(s) or company storing these files, and cannot prosecute any person(s) affiliated with this website. Amendments 9 and 10 of The United States Bill Of Rights protect the right to be free of unwarranted and unwanted government intrusion into one's personal and private affairs, papers, and possessions. Article 12 of The United Nations Universal Declaration of Human Rights states, No one shall be subjected to arbitrary interference with his privacy, family, home or correspondence, nor to attacks upon his honor and reputation. Everyone has the right to the protection of the law against such interference or attacks.

#### What information we collect

Whilst using the XtremePapers website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * Geographical location
  * Browser type and version
  * Operating system
  * Referral source
  * Length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to XtremePapers Community is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

#### How we use cookies and IP addresses

XtremePapers, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address.

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use XtremePapers Community and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit XtremePapers Community and any associated websites and sub-domains are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

#### Links to other websites

XtremePapers, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with XtremePapers.

XtremePapers has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and XtremePapers cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

#### Controlling your personal information

When using the XtremePapers Community, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

XtremePapers will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission to do so. We may use your personal information to send you information, or other information pertaining to XtremePapers, or your account.

If you discover any of the information XtremePapers holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.
